

# MARIUS STRYDOM

#### CONTACT

Address: Auckland, Clarks Beach 2122

**Phone**: (+64) 027 447 0182 **Email**: marius@aptwrite.nz

#### **SKILLS**

 Technical Writing, Article Writing, Editing,

Strong research skills, Fact-checking

· Microsoft 365, Microsoft Office

• HTML5, CSS, Markdown

 Content Creation, Media design, GIMP, Inkscape

• Clear Communication

 Adaptability and Flexibility, Willingness to Learn

Team Collaboration

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Versatile and technical content writer proficient in researching, writing, and editing diverse content. Capable of producing engaging, authoritative, and error-free work independently. Highly communicative with a 11-year track record of delivering superior performance in remote environments.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Freelance Article Writer, 06/2023 to 08/2023 Bay of Plenty Business Publications - Tauranga

• Research and write 3 articles about local (Bay of Plenty) celebrities.

### **Technical Writer,** 06/2013 to Current **New Zealand Metal Roofing Manufacturers Association** - Auckland

- Using technical writing skills to contribute to the ongoing improvement, accuracy, and relevance of the NZMRM Metal Roof and Wall Cladding Code of Practice (NZMRM CoP).
- · Continuing to do so by facilitating and managing quarterly updates.
- Enhanced the accessibility and usability of the NZMRM CoP by digitising the original (pdf) document.
- Adapting communication strategies to liaise with subject-matter experts, web designers, and graphic artists.
- Rewriting content, copy editing and formatting content for the association website.
- · Design templates and layouts.
- Edit and manipulate graphics, illustrations, and photographs for publication.

# Interviewer and Role Assessor, 02/2020 to 10/2023 Technical Advisory Services (TAS) to Te Whata Ora and Public Services Commission of NZ - Wellington

- · Interview pay equity claimants and comparison roles
- Write interview transcriptions
- Regularly met with other assessors (including union representatives) to assess claimants and comparator roles according to a fair rating system.

#### **EDUCATION**

New Zealand Certificate in Information Technology (level4), 12/2007 Open Polytechnic of NZ - Wellington, WGN

Certificate in Technical Communication (Level5), 01/2007 Open Polytechnic of NZ - Wellington

**B.A. Communications**, 08/1988 **University of Johannesburg** - Johannesburg, South Africa

## **REFERENCES**

Available on request